{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Glass \u0026 Shower Door Installation Pros","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40068/":{"taskOID":40068,"originalTaskOID":40068,"setID":390,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":1483,"questionDisplayText":"Type of enclosure","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Choose the kind of glass shower doors you need installed.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":988,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bathtub","answerDisplayText":"Bathtub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5644,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Shower","answerDisplayText":"Shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1502,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Combination tub/shower","answerDisplayText":"Combination tub/shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6066,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Steam shower","answerDisplayText":"Steam shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1485,"questionDisplayText":"Glass Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of glass?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1421,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Clear","answerDisplayText":"Clear","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4324,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Obscured","answerDisplayText":"Obscured","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2808,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Glass block","answerDisplayText":"Glass block","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2256,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Etched","answerDisplayText":"Etched","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1486,"questionDisplayText":"Configuration","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the configuration of the unit?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5785,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sliding by-pass doors","answerDisplayText":"Sliding by-pass doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3020,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Hinged door with adjacent fixed glass panel","answerDisplayText":"Hinged door with adjacent fixed glass panel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3019,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Hinged door with 2 adjacent fixed glass panels","answerDisplayText":"Hinged door with 2 adjacent fixed glass panels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3018,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hinged door (alone)","answerDisplayText":"Hinged door (alone)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1484,"questionDisplayText":"Door and Panel Types","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of door and panel(s)?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2623,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Frameless (3/8\" or 1/2\" glass)","answerDisplayText":"Frameless (3/8\" or 1/2\" glass)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":761,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Aluminum frame (1/4\" glass)","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum frame (1/4\" glass)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":1483,"questionDisplayText":"Type of enclosure","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Choose the kind of glass shower doors you need installed.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":988,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bathtub","answerDisplayText":"Bathtub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5644,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Shower","answerDisplayText":"Shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1502,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Combination tub/shower","answerDisplayText":"Combination tub/shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6066,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Steam shower","answerDisplayText":"Steam shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":988,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bathtub","answerDisplayText":"Bathtub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5644,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Shower","answerDisplayText":"Shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1502,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Combination tub/shower","answerDisplayText":"Combination tub/shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6066,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Steam shower","answerDisplayText":"Steam shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1485,"questionDisplayText":"Glass Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of glass?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1421,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Clear","answerDisplayText":"Clear","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4324,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Obscured","answerDisplayText":"Obscured","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2808,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Glass block","answerDisplayText":"Glass block","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2256,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Etched","answerDisplayText":"Etched","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1421,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Clear","answerDisplayText":"Clear","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4324,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Obscured","answerDisplayText":"Obscured","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2808,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Glass block","answerDisplayText":"Glass block","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2256,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Etched","answerDisplayText":"Etched","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1486,"questionDisplayText":"Configuration","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the configuration of the unit?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5785,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sliding by-pass doors","answerDisplayText":"Sliding by-pass doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3020,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Hinged door with adjacent fixed glass panel","answerDisplayText":"Hinged door with adjacent fixed glass panel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3019,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Hinged door with 2 adjacent fixed glass panels","answerDisplayText":"Hinged door with 2 adjacent fixed glass panels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3018,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hinged door (alone)","answerDisplayText":"Hinged door (alone)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5785,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sliding by-pass doors","answerDisplayText":"Sliding by-pass doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3020,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Hinged door with adjacent fixed glass panel","answerDisplayText":"Hinged door with adjacent fixed glass panel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3019,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Hinged door with 2 adjacent fixed glass panels","answerDisplayText":"Hinged door with 2 adjacent fixed glass panels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3018,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hinged door (alone)","answerDisplayText":"Hinged door (alone)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1484,"questionDisplayText":"Door and Panel Types","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of door and panel(s)?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2623,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Frameless (3/8\" or 1/2\" glass)","answerDisplayText":"Frameless (3/8\" or 1/2\" glass)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":761,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Aluminum frame (1/4\" glass)","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum frame (1/4\" glass)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2623,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Frameless (3/8\" or 1/2\" glass)","answerDisplayText":"Frameless (3/8\" or 1/2\" glass)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":761,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Aluminum frame (1/4\" glass)","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum frame (1/4\" glass)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"__cache./api/resource/task/40068/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40068,"taskName":"Glass Shower Door or Enclosure - Install","taskDescription":"Install or Replace a Shower Door or Enclosure","xmTaskDescriptor":"Glass \u0026 Shower Door Installation Pros","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":106,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Glass Door mirror Enclosure Shower","textMessagingName":"Inst Glass Shower","rolloverLongDesc":"Handled by some remodelers \u0026 many glass specialists.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes door, frame \u0026 surrounding glass.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace a Shower Door or Enclosure.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Glass Shower Door Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Shower Enclosure","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":38,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Glass Shower Door or Enclosure Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Glass Shower Door or Enclosure - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Glass Shower Door Project","urlName":"Glass-Shower-Door-or-Enclosure-Install","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Glass Shower Door Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Shower Enclosure Installation","searchKeywords":"Glass,Door,mirror,Enclosure,Shower,bathroom,bathrub,bypass,sliding","emcCategoryOid":-12037,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":390,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}